okay so I think we're starting our
好吧，我想我们正在开始
livestream
现场直播
okay let me just set things up here a
好吧，让我在这里设置一下
little bit give me a moment
给我一点时间
okay so um welcome everyone I don't see
好吧，嗯，欢迎没有见到的每个人
how many people has have joined but
有多少人参加了
hopefully you can hear me loud and
希望你能听到我的声音
Creole clear we're on our second Jakarta
克里奥尔语清楚，我们正在第二次雅加达
tech talk this time with James rapper
这次与James Rapper进行技术交流
and he is going to talk to us about
他将和我们谈谈
reactive with getting reactive with
与...反应
streams in Jakarta EE so James do you
流在雅加达EE中，所以詹姆斯
want to take it over share your screen
想要接管分享您的屏幕
and and start present yep perfect just
并且开始现在是完美的
for everyone please feel free to use
对于每个人，请随时使用
chat after James finishes we'll have
詹姆斯讲完后，我们聊聊
everything open for questions and
一切都充满疑问和
answers and I'm sure we'll be happy to
答案，我相信我们会很高兴
answer your questions okay so thank you
回答您的问题好吧，谢谢
for joining my name is James rota if
因为我的名字叫詹姆斯·罗塔，如果
you're on the East Coast I understand
你在东海岸，我了解
the afternoon if you're on the west
下午，如果你在西边
coast the morning if you're in Europe
如果您在欧洲，请在早晨到海岸
it's probably late in the evening and if
可能是晚上很晚，如果
you're where I am in Australia then I do
你就是我在澳大利亚的地方
recommend going outside and watching the
建议去外面看
sunrise well you hear this webinar so I
日出，您听到了这次网络研讨会，所以我
work for a company called light Bend we
在一家名为Light Bend的公司工作
the company behind the scholar program
学者计划背后的公司
in language between behind our Kerr play
在我们的克尔戏剧背后的语言之间
framework and logon and my role there is
框架和登录，我的角色是
the open source software architecture
开源软件架构
today we're going to be looking at some
今天我们将要看一些
upcoming reactive specifications in
即将发布的反应规范
Jakarta AE focusing specifically on some
雅加达AE专门针对一些
specifications that are both finished
都完成的规格
and in progress and my profile that we
以及进行中和我的个人资料
hope will be eventually adopted into
希望最终将被采纳
Jakarta AE and can be
雅加达AE和可以
used in popular Jakarta AE or Java EE
在流行的Jakarta AE或Java EE中使用
application service today so the first
今天的应用服务第一
thing we're going to look at is is what
我们要看的是什么
is really active what do we mean when we
真的很活跃，当我们
say we're going to bring reactive to
说我们要带动反应
Jakarta AE we're going to then look at
雅加达AE，我们接下来要看
what reactive streams is which is a
什么是反应性流
particular technology for for doing
特定的做事技术
reactive programming and we're going to
反应式编程，我们将
look at exactly how this is being used
看看到底是怎么使用的
some completed specs and some in
一些完整的规格和一些
progress specs so what is reactive now
进度规范，所以现在有什么反应
when a lot of people when reactive comes
当很多人反应过来时
to mind probably a lot of people will
要记住很多人会
think eventually I oh so things like
我想我最终还是这样
completion stage and completable future
完成阶段和可完成的未来
things like if you've heard of reactive
如果您听说过反应式的话
streams
流
asynchronous handling of advanced acing
异步处理高级Acing
of this back pressure perhaps the Java
这种背压也许是Java
you a are IRAP eyes and the the
您是IRAP的眼睛，
asynchronous event of an i/o
I / O的异步事件
capabilities there and you would be
能力在那里，你会
right if you if you thought that that's
对，如果你认为那是
reactive because it is but one problem
反应性的，因为这只是一个问题
that that we say today is is that people
我们今天说的是
stop at that and they say event-driven
停下来，他们说事件驱动
IO is all reactive is and that's in no
IO都是反应性的，那不是
way true reactive is so much more in
真正的反应性在很大程度上
fact if you just stop at an event-driven
事实上，如果您只是停止在事件驱动下
IO you actually don't get much value at
IO，您实际上并没有获得太多价值
all you you're able to perhaps use your
所有您可能使用的
hardware a little better about the full
硬件更好一些
potential of reactive offers so much
反应性报价的潜力如此之大
more so reactive is a set of
更具反应性的是
architectural patterns for building
建筑的建筑图案
systems that are responsive so
反应灵敏的系统
responsive means when you go to the
响应式意味着您去
system regardless of what else is
系统，不管是什么
happening
发生
the system it should give you an answer
系统应该给你答案
it should work in within a reasonable
它应该在合理的范围内工作
timeframe and in order to achieve that
时间框架并为了实现这一目标
it needs to be resilient so if there is
它需要有弹性，所以如果有
a failure in the component in this
组件中的故障
system it shouldn't bring the whole
系统不应该带来整体
system down it should be able to
系统关闭它应该能够
continue working even when failures
即使出现故障也可以继续工作
occur and secondly it also to be
发生，其次也是
responsive it needs to be scalable both
响应性，它既需要扩展，又需要扩展
up and down because we don't want to
上下，因为我们不想
it's no good to be able to just be
能够成为一个人是不好的
having 100 100 machines running a system
有100100台计算机正在运行一个系统
that that only needs that one day a year
一年只需要一天
and so these are these properties of
这些就是这些的特性
resilience and scalability underline
弹性和可扩展性强调
what a reactive system should be and
什么是反应系统？
it'll ease those tenants of reactive
缓解那些反应式的租户
it's perfectly suited to solving the
非常适合解决
challenges of cloud native systems and
云原生系统的挑战
in case you aren't aware there is
如果你不知道那里
something called the reactive manifesto
所谓的反应性宣言
which very neatly and succinctly
非常简洁明了
summarizes what reactive is and why it's
总结什么是反应性及其原因
needed so you can visit that WWWE active
需要，以便您可以访问该WWWE active
manifesto dot organ in your own time if
您自己的时间里的宣言器官
you wish so let's look at some of these
您希望如此，让我们看一下其中的一些
challenges that we have in in cloud
云中的挑战
native computing that reactive seeks
反应性寻求的本机计算
itself so quite a native opens many
本身就是一个本地人
opportunities the what we can do when we
机会，当我们
go to the cloud compared to just running
与仅运行相比，上云
on our own servers is his far is very
在我们自己的服务器上是他的非常非常
broad but it also introduces many
广泛，但同时也引入了许多
challenges so I'm not going to talk
挑战，所以我不会说话
about all the challenges but some
关于所有挑战，但有些挑战
examples are when you go to the cloud
例子是当你去云端
and you're running micro services you
并且您正在运行微服务
don't have a single database ok and
没有一个数据库好，并且
because you don't have a single database
因为你没有一个数据库
you don't have acid transactions on your
你没有酸交易
dad only on your global state now you
爸爸现在只有你的全球状态
might have each service that your that
可能会提供您的每项服务
you're running might have its own
你在跑步可能有它自己的
database and within that database you
数据库，在该数据库中，您
didn't have acid transactions for
没有酸交易
updates but because you have multiple
更新，但因为您有多个
databases when you need to update
需要更新时的数据库
multiple services there's no way to do
多种服务是没有办法做的
that in an atomic way you don't have
以原子的方式，你没有
acid transactions across all your
您所有的酸交易
services and so consistency can no
服务，所以一致性不可能
longer be taken for granted another
不再理所当然
challenge is that because you've got
挑战是因为你有
more services you've got more Network
提供更多服务的更多网络
and communication you've got more
和沟通，您将获得更多
deployment configuration there's more
部署配置还有更多
moving parts and so there's more that
运动部件，所以还有更多
you can get wrong and so consequently
您可能会出错，因此
cloud native systems are inherently more
云原生系统本质上更多
fragile they're inherently more prone to
脆弱，它们本来就更容易
failure now people often talk about
失败现在人们经常谈论
going to the cloud and because you've
去云，因为你已经
got so many machines there you can build
有那么多机器可以建造
a more resilient application but that
更具弹性的应用程序，但是
doesn't happen automatically
不会自动发生
if you don't carefully design and use
如果您不仔细设计和使用
patterns that allow you to take
可以让你采取的模式
advantage of those machines to build a
这些机器的优势
more resilient system you won't end up
永无止境的更具弹性的系统
with a more resilient system you will
有了更具弹性的系统，您将
end up with a far more fragile system
最终导致系统更加脆弱
than a typical traditional monolith
比典型的传统巨石
clamo does offer great opportunities to
clamo确实为
scale on on most common clouds the the
在最常见的云上扩展
resources at least compared to what you
资源至少与您相比
usually need seemingly endless but these
通常需要看似无尽的东西，但是这些
but scaling also doesn't happen
但也不会发生缩放
automatically how do you do so
自动如何
horizontally if you just apply your
如果你只是应用你的水平
normal patterns that you had with a
您使用的正常模式
monolith you'll find you run into
巨石，你会发现你遇到
bottlenecks very quickly
瓶颈很快
so I'm going to outline just a couple of
所以我只概述几个
principles in reactive there are there
反应性原理有
are reactive is far bigger than this but
反应性远大于此，但
a couple of principles that reactive the
反应性的几个原则
architecting reactive systems that we
设计我们的反应系统
use when we architectural active systems
在我们构建活动系统时使用
that help to solve some of these
有助于解决其中一些问题
challenges probably the biggest
挑战最大
principle in reactive is isolating
反应原理是隔离
services and when we say isolate we mean
服务，当我们说孤立时，我们的意思是
ensuring that these services can't have
确保这些服务不能
an impact on each other so let's just
互相影响，让我们
look at the moment at HTTP communication
看一下HTTP通讯
it's very common when building micro
在构建微型计算机时非常常见
services in the cloud to use HTTP G RPC
云中的服务以使用HTTP G RPC
is also becoming common but these these
也变得普遍，但是这些
protocols are inherently synchronous it
协议本质上是同步的
doesn't matter if you're using
不管你在用
asynchronous i/o you're still doing a
异步I / O，您仍在执行
request on the remote system in a
在远程系统上的请求
response and if that system isn't
响应，如果该系统不是
running at the time that it's not
在没有的时候运行
available if it's not responsive you
如果没有响应您可用
won't be able to proceed with your
将无法继续您的
operation so HTTP depends on both
操作，因此HTTP取决于两者
services involved in the communication
沟通中涉及的服务
being responsive and this offers an
反应灵敏，这提供了一个
opportunity for full fragility because
充分脆弱的机会，因为
of one of those services goes down then
其中一项服务发生故障，然后
effectively both services down you can't
有效地两种服务都无法解决
achieve the operation that you need to
实现您需要的操作
if you use an HTTP to communicate
如果您使用HTTP进行通讯
between them and this gets worse if you
他们之间，如果你
start involving more and more services
开始涉及越来越多的服务
because each service that that has an
因为每个具有
HTTP call done to work whether it's in
完成HTTP调用即可正常工作
sequence or transitively is going to
顺序或传递要
impact the overall availability of the
影响整体的可用性
system so when you use HTTP for
系统，因此当您将HTTP用于
communication between services you don't
您不需要的服务之间的通信
have isolation okay HTTP is not a
有隔离好吗HTTP不是
reactive architectural principle
反应性建筑原理
so you might think well we'll use a
所以您可能会认为我们将使用
message broker to to communicate between
消息代理之间进行通信
services and that's um that's a good
服务，那是很好的
idea
理念
and so you might as part of your
所以你可能会成为你的一部分
operation you might update some state in
操作，您可能会更新一些状态
your local database and then publish a
您的本地数据库，然后发布一个
message to a message broker there's
给消息经纪人的消息
still a dependency here because it means
这里仍然是一个依赖，因为这意味着
the service that is trying to complete
试图完成的服务
the operation must be responsive at the
该操作必须在
same time is the message broker and if
同时是消息代理，如果
for example that service doesn't
例如服务不
operation and then tries to publish a
操作，然后尝试发布
message to the message broker and the
消息给消息代理和
message broker isn't responsive then
然后，消息代理没有响应
that operation is going to only
该操作只会
partially complete whichever order you
部分完成您的订单
happen to do it in maybe you disable a
碰巧这样做可能是因为您禁用了
CalPERS haven't published to the message
CalPERS尚未发布消息
broker first and then commit my
经纪人，然后提交我的
transaction and let's say that this
交易，让我们说这
published to the message broker succeeds
发布到消息代理成功
but then you your database transaction
但是然后你你的数据库事务
fails then you you still have a
失败了，那么你仍然有一个
partially complete operation and so it's
部分完成操作，所以
better because usually it's easier to
更好，因为通常更容易
keep a piece of infrastructure like a
保持像
message broker available but you still
消息代理可用，但您仍然
don't have complete isolation there so
那里没有完全隔离
what we really wanted to try and do is
我们真正想要尝试做的是
make all operations asynchronous and and
使所有操作异步进行，并且
this is done using CQRS so if you can
这是使用CQRS完成的，因此，如果可以
separate your commands so the things
分开您的命令，使事情
that come in and update your local stage
进来并更新您的本地舞台
from queries and that includes
从查询中，其中包括
publishing messages to a message broker
将消息发布到消息代理
then you end up having no dependency
那你就没有依赖性了
between the responsiveness of any
之间的任何响应
component and you achieve full failure
组件，您完全失败
and scale in isolation and are able to
孤立地扩展并能够
take the full advantage of your cloud
充分利用您的云
native platform the second principle
本机平台第二个原则
that I want to talk about is adopting
我想谈的是采用
programming models that manage failure
管理故障的编程模型
so in a traditional system in a monolith
所以在传统系统中
perhaps running Java a a or or not acid
也许运行Java aa或不酸
transactions are there to handle failure
交易在那里处理失败
for you a developer doesn't need to
对您来说，开发人员不需要
explicitly handle all the failure
明确处理所有失败
conditions they don't need to anticipate
他们不需要预期的条件
all the possibilities what happens if
所有的可能性，如果发生
something else tries to update this at
其他东西试图在更新
the same time what happens if either my
在同一时间，如果我的
service or the database goes down
服务或数据库故障
halfway through they don't need to worry
中途他们不必担心
about what do I need to clean that clean
关于我需要怎样清洁
up if there is a failure
如果出现故障，则向上
what compensating actions do I need to
我需要什么补偿措施
do do I need to retry the transactions
我需要重试交易吗
handle that for you but as we said
为您处理，但正如我们所说
before in cloud native systems we don't
以前在云原生系统中我们不
have asset transactions at a system
在系统中进行资产交易
level and so the moment that we need to
水平，所以我们需要的那一刻
do an update that involves multiple
进行涉及多个的更新
services we no longer have anything that
服务，我们不再拥有任何
managers failure for us but we do want
经理对我们失败，但我们确实想要
something that manages further for us
对我们来说更重要的事情
because we don't want to have to
因为我们不想
manually implement handling for all the
手动实施所有
permutations of failure conditions they
失效条件的排列
could happen and so we need a different
可能会发生，所以我们需要一个不同的
pattern for managing failure one that
管理失败的模式之一
isn't manual one that that we can take
不是我们可以接受的手册
for granted that we can focus on solving
理所当然地，我们可以专注于解决
our business problem
我们的业务问题
so I might I think I had a problem with
所以我可能觉得我有一个问题
my heads up there sir streams have a
我的头在那里，先生流有一个
cloud native equivalent of acid
云天然酸当量
transactions in am streams are an
流中的交易是
architectural pattern that we can use to
我们可以用来的建筑模式
be able to not worry about failure
不用担心失败
anymore so let's take a look at this
不再，所以让我们来看看
reactive streams you may have heard of
您可能听说过的反应性流
is is a an approach to scrape the
是一种刮擦
streaming that is reactive both from the
来自
programming perspective and then end
编程角度，然后结束
from a systems architectural perspective
从系统架构的角度
at a high level
在高水平
reactive streams offer a declarative way
反应性流提供了一种声明性方式
of describing work to be done and this a
描述要完成的工作，这是一个
declarative way of describing work is
描述性的工作描述方式是
important because what you don't want to
重要，因为您不想
be doing is saying okay I'm going to for
这样做是在说我要去
example read some message and then I'm
示例阅读一些消息，然后我
going to process it and then I'm going
要处理它，然后我要去
to send a message here because if you're
在这里发送消息，因为如果你
the one that that's controlling what
控制什么的那个
what's done when then you also have to
什么时候做，那么你还必须
manage the failure rather you don't what
处理失败，而不管你什么
you just want to do is declare well here
你只想做的就是在这里声明好
is my processing for those messages and
是我对这些消息的处理，
I want to let the infrastructure go and
我想放开基础设施
handle life cycle and failure and
处理生命周期和失败，
retries for me and distribution as well
重试并分发给我
because when we go to the cloud we
因为当我们去云端时
potentially have many machines and we
可能有很多机器，我们
don't want to have to to manually spread
不想手动传播
that word across their machines
他们机器上的那个词
ourselves reactive streams offers
我们自己的反应流提供
asynchronous handling of events so it
异步处理事件，因此
ensures that we have efficiency of
确保我们的效率
resource use if we we can run many
如果我们可以运行很多资源
streams at once without consuming many
一次流而不消耗很多
threads
线程数
and reactive streams also propagates
反应性流也传播
back pressure and back pressure
背压和背压
propagation is very important because
传播非常重要，因为
without a back propagating back pressure
没有背传播的背压
there's no way for a downstream
没有下游的方法
processor or consumer of data to be able
处理者或数据使用者
to push back to upstream processes and
推回上游流程，并
say hey I'm not ready to receive more
说嘿我还没有准备好接收更多
data yet can you please slow down there
数据还可以，请您慢下来
are some api's in Jakarta ae at the
是在雅加达ae的一些api
moment that offer asynchronous handling
提供异步处理的时刻
of events without that pressure and so
没有这种压力的事件等等
the websocket api for example there's no
例如，websocket api没有
way to go back to a WebSocket and say
回到WebSocket并说
hey can you actually push back on the
嘿，你真的可以推开
TCP connection to stop the client from
TCP连接以阻止客户端从
sending me Danny you have to handle it
给我丹尼，你必须处理
all and if you can't will are they going
全部，如果不能，他们会去吗
to run out of memory or you're going to
耗尽内存，否则您将
somehow or you just have to fail so in
不知何故，或者你只是必须失败，所以在
an implementation level reactive streams
实现级别的反应流
is a specification effort that was
是一项规范工作，
started by light Bend Netflix and
由light Bend Netflix和
pivotal and others in 2013
关键和其他在2013
that's 2013 when the initial contact and
那是2013年，最初的接触和
discussions were made and then in it was
进行了讨论，然后在其中
worked on through 2014 and finally
一直工作到2014年，最后
released in 2015
2015年发布
it was adopted in Java and JDK 9 and so
它已在Java和JDK 9中采用，因此
you can find this today in the Java util
您今天可以在Java util中找到它
concurrent flow API it's considered a
并发流API被认为是
low level integration API so so the
低级集成API，因此
interfaces in in Java util concurrent
Java util并发中的接口
flow there are 4 interfaces publisher
流有4个界面发布者
subscriber subscription and there's also
订户订阅，还有
processor which is just a implements
只是一个工具的处理器
both publisher and subscriber and
发布者和订阅者以及
there's only I think 7 methods across
我认为只有7种方法
these interfaces but these interfaces
这些接口，但是这些接口
intended for use for integrating between
用于整合
different
不同
asynchronous streaming libraries so if I
异步流库，所以如果我
have a database that is able to
有一个能够
asynchronously stream me rows and I have
异步流我行，我有
a HTTP client that is able to
一个能够执行以下操作的HTTP客户端
asynchronously stream out but and then I
异步流出，然后我
have a stream manipulation library
有一个流操作库
that's able able to do a single
能够做一个
transform a transformations that that
改变那种
should convert these rows to bytes I can
应该将这些行转换为字节我可以
connect all these things together using
将所有这些东西连接在一起
reactive streams even if the authors of
反应流，即使
these technologies had never heard of
这些技术从未听说过
had never heard of or tested each other
从未听说过或互相测试过
against each other and that's what
互相对抗，就是这样
reactive streams offers it does require
反应性流提供确实需要的
high level user-facing api's an
面向用户的高级api是
important a point to make is that users
重要的一点是，用户
should never implement reactive stream
永远不要实现反应流
interfaces directly themselves if you're
如果您是
using reactive streams and you find
使用反应流，您会发现
yourself implementing a publisher or
您自己实施发布者，或
subscriber then you're probably doing
订户，那么您可能正在做
things wrong because these there's even
事情错了，因为这些甚至
though it's only a few interfaces and
虽然只有几个界面
about seven methods the spec for
规格约有七种方法
reactive streams itself has a forty or
反应性流本身有40或
fifty individual requirements there's a
五十个人的要求有一个
TCK that kept there can be one against
保留在那里的TCK可以反对
against this there's an implementation
对此有一个实现
which includes around hundred tests and
其中包括约一百项测试
getting them to pass is is a lot of
让他们通过是很多
effort it's a lot of concurrent
大量的并发
programming merit dealing with memory
处理内存的编程优势
barriers it's not intended for users to
它不适合用户使用的障碍
implement directly themselves whether
直接实施自己是否
they need a high level user facing API
他们需要面向用户的高级API
unfortunately they are there are plenty
不幸的是，他们有很多
out there so you have your connectors to
在那里，所以您有连接器
databases to message brokers to to HTTP
数据库到消息代理到HTTP
clients that then implement reactive
然后实施反应式的客户
streams and you also have streams
流，你也有流
manipulation libraries such as ARCA
操纵库，例如ARCA
streams Eric's Java and reactor so when
流Eric的Java和反应堆，所以当
you do work with the reactive streams
您可以使用反应流
you can bring in these libraries and do
您可以引入这些库并执行
whatever transformations you need on the
您需要的任何转换
streams
流
of course when it comes to Jakarta a a a
当然，对于雅加达aaa
challenge here is that these are all
这里的挑战是这些都是
vendor library's proprietary libraries
供应商库的专有库
they may be open source but they're not
他们可能是开源的，但不是
standards they're not something that can
标准，他们不是可以
just be included in a Jakarta AAA
只包含在雅加达AAA中
implementation and so to address this in
实施，因此在
micro profile I'm going to introduce our
微型个人资料我将介绍我们的
first specification and that's Mike
第一个规格，就是迈克
profile reactive strains operators so
轮廓反应应变算符
this specification is a high level user
该规范是高级用户
facing API for manipulating reactive
面对API来操纵反应式
streams we've just released 1.0 so you
流，我们刚刚发布了1.0，所以您
can use it there are a number of
可以使用它有很多
implementations out there that you can
你可以在那里实现
try it draws inspiration from Java util
尝试从Java util中汲取灵感
streams so if you're familiar with Java
流，因此，如果您熟悉Java
util streams then a lot of the methods
util流然后有很多方法
are the same the scope of what methods
范围是什么方法都一样
are included and what aren't are the
包括在内，什么不是
same I should point out that even though
同样，我应该指出，即使
the api's looks similar the unlined of
api的外观类似
of what you're actually doing is is very
你实际上在做的是非常
different so Java util streams is about
不同，因此Java util流是关于
manipulating collections of of things
操纵事物的集合
that are usually in memory or they're
通常在内存中或者
some or they're calculated somehow
一些或以某种方式计算
on-the-fly
即时
potentially in parallel it's about bulk
潜在地并行它是关于批量
processing operations of that don't
的处理操作不
involve IO reactive streams on the on
涉及IO反应流
the other hand is about fundamentally
另一方面从根本上讲
about handling IO about being able to
关于如何处理IO
process things asynchronously about
异步处理事物
being able to push back up the stream
能够向后推流
with back pressure reactive streams the
与背压反应流
implementation combines the best of ARCA
实施结合了ARCA的优势
streams rxjava and reactors so every
流rxjava和反应堆，所以每个
feature that we added we looked at all
我们添加的功能我们查看了所有
those three of these popular
这三个受欢迎的
implementations and we looked at okay
实现，我们看着还好
what naming convention do they use what
他们使用什么命名约定
are their what are their edge cases how
他们的优势是什么？
they handle different things and
他们处理不同的事情，
and try to come up with whatever was was
并尝试提出曾经是什么
common and and whatever seems to to fit
普通的，似乎合适的东西
best based on the experiences of those
最好根据那些人的经验
laborers and we have three
劳工，我们有三个
implementations so far so there's one
到目前为止的实现
that's our custom supposed one that's
这是我们的习惯，假设是
our X Java based and we've got another
我们基于X Java的应用程序
one that doesn't have any dependencies
一个没有任何依赖性的
so it's been implemented from scratch
所以它是从头开始实现的
and the intention for that one is if
而这个目的是
this was to ever to be adopted into the
这将永远被采纳为
jdk itself that might become the
jdk本身可能会成为
reference implementation so what I will
参考实施，所以我会
do now is take a look at some of a P I
现在要做的就是看一些PI
docked for these so here is processor
停靠这些，所以这里是处理器
builder this is for a processor builders
这是给处理器建造者的
for building generic transformations so
用于构建通用转换，因此
the kind of methods that you have are
你所拥有的方法是
things like map you can see we have
像地图这样的东西，你可以看到我们有
these diagrams for what it actually
这些图实际上是什么
looks like so you have an incoming
看起来像这样你有一个传入
stream that has elements 1 5 &amp; 3 and if
具有元素1 5和3的流，如果
the map transformation is to multiply it
地图转换是将其相乘
by 10 you get out 10 50 and 30 an
乘以10，您得出10、50和30
example of a flat map we can see down
我们可以看到平面图的示例
here are the ones filter so filter
这是过滤器，所以过滤器
everything that's less than 3 and so
所有小于3的东西
these are these are the kinds of
这些是这些的
operations that we have skip 3 elements
我们跳过的操作3个元素
so the first 3 skipped and then you get
所以前三个跳过，然后你得到
2 &amp; 4 out now I could give a demo of
现在我可以进行2和4的演示
these but chances are if you are
这些，但是如果你是
familiar with Java 8 and went to any
熟悉Java 8，并去过任何
conferences around the time the Java
Java周围的会议
rate was the last you've probably seen
率是您可能见过的最后一个
plenty of demos of Java util streams and
Java util流的大量演示，以及
that's not much different from just
这与只是没有太大的不同
using micro profile reactive streams
使用微轮廓反应流
operators in isolation the code looks
运算符孤立的代码看起来
very similar to the same sort of methods
与同类方法非常相似
and using restrooms operators out of the
并使用洗手间操作员
context of actually doing asynchronous
实际执行异步的上下文
i/o process in
输入/输出过程
really isn't interesting you're much
你真的很有趣
better off using java.util streams so
使用java.util流更好
before I give a demo of this this API
在我对此API进行演示之前
I'd like to move on to the next spec
我想继续下一个规格
which is something that actually uses
这是实际使用的东西
and provides a use case for those
并为这些人提供用例
operators to do some IO processing and
操作员进行一些IO处理
that's micro profile reactive messaging
这是微个人资料反应式消息传递
so it's it's a reactive streams based
所以这是一个基于反应的流
messaging API messaging as in
消息传递API消息传递，如
communicating through a message broker
通过消息代理进行通信
or through doing messaging peer-to-peer
或通过对等消息传递
it essentially provides two annotations
它本质上提供了两个注释
incoming and outgoing you put these on
传入和传出你把这些
methods in a CDI beam and that declares
CDI梁中的方法并声明
this this method provides something
这种方法提供了一些东西
that's going to handle incoming or
这将处理传入或
outgoing messages I can be connected to
我可以连接到的外发邮件
any messaging provider so we have
任何消息传递提供商，所以我们有
implementations for Kafka a MPP and QT t
Kafka a MPP和QT t的实现
JM acid there's there's there's as it's
JM酸的存在的存在
been designed so that it's not tied to
设计成不与
any one messaging provider the spec is
规范的任何一个消息传递提供商
currently in development and we're
目前正在开发中，我们正在
targeting micro profile 3.0 for it and
针对它的微型配置文件3.0和
so I'll now move on to a demo so I've
所以我现在继续演示，我已经
got an application here so this is an
在这里有一个应用程序，所以这是一个
online option it's somewhat like eBay so
在线选项有点像eBay，所以
I'm just going to create an item here I
我要在这里创建一个项目
want to auction off my bike it is if at
想拍卖我的自行车，如果
any we're going to check the chat as
任何我们要检查的聊天方式
well with some questions that would be
很好的一些问题是
great or maybe afterwards after the the
伟大的，也许之后
the demo I'll do it afterwards perfect
演示，之后我会做的完美
thanks so I've created an auction it's
谢谢，所以我创建了一个拍卖
i'm selling my red bike i'll start the
我在卖我的红色自行车，我将开始
auction and now if it's very secure
拍卖，如果现在非常安全
authentication
认证方式
got a log in as a different user I'll
以其他用户身份登录
place a beard $10 bead you can see
放一副10美元的胡须
currently that's been accepted with a
目前已被接受
price of 50 cents and then if I go and
50美分的价格，然后如果我去
log in as someone else now let's say
现在以其他人的身份登录
this John user goes and they're really
这个约翰使用者去了，他们真的
interested in red icons so they search
对红色图标感兴趣，因此他们进行搜索
and my black comes up now you see here
现在我的黑色出现了，你在这里看到
the current price is not listed and the
当前价格未列出，
reason is because I have failed to
原因是因为我没有
implement something in this service so
在此服务中实现一些东西
we have a number of services
我们有很多服务
implementing this application and there
实施此应用程序并在那里
is an auction service that or an item
是一项拍卖服务
service that holds the details of the
包含以下详细信息的服务
item there's an auction a bidding
拍卖项目
service that that controls bids and
控制出价的服务以及
there's a search service that implements
有一个实施的搜索服务
this search screen and the way the
此搜索屏幕以及
search service gets as information is by
搜索服务获取信息的依据
subscribing to kafka topics that from
订阅来自
both the item service to get the
两者都获得服务
information of the items as well as the
项目的信息以及
bidding service to get the current price
竞价服务以获取当前价格
so if we go and have a look at the code
所以如果我们去看看代码
this is where it's subscribing to the
这是订阅的地方
bidding service so you can see here
竞标服务，因此您可以在这里看到
current we've got this incoming
目前我们已经收到了
annotation and it's saying I want the
注释，这是说我想要
bidding relevant topic this is returning
出价相关主题正在返回
a subscriber builder so this is the
订户生成器，所以这是
micro profile reactive streams operators
微轮廓反应流操作员
API here it's going to build a
这里的API将建立一个
subscriber of of bid events and then we
投标事件的订户，然后我们
create the Builder here and you can see
在这里创建生成器，您可以看到
we're doing nothing with each message so
我们对每条消息都不做任何事情，所以
obviously we we haven't implemented it
显然我们还没有实施
yet we have implemented here up up here
但是我们已经在这里实现了
the item event processing so that's why
项目事件处理，这就是为什么
the item appears and the search index at
出现该项目，搜索索引位于
all but the prices and appearing because
除了价格以外，其他所有原因都是因为
we haven't yet implemented handling of
我们尚未实施
the bid events which have contained the
包含以下内容的出价事件
price in them
价格在他们
so why don't we do that so the first
那么为什么我们不这样做呢？
thing that we want to do when we receive
我们收到时想要做的事情
a bad bit of that this some service
这服务有些不好
actually persists its data inside
实际上将其数据保留在内部
elasticsearch and elasticsearch works
elasticsearch和elasticsearch作品
with documents so we want to first
与文件，所以我们想先
convert our messages using the map
使用地图转换我们的消息
function into documents so I've already
功能进入文档，所以我已经
created a method to do that great event
创建了一种方法来处理重大事件
to document now this method actually
现在要记录这个方法
doesn't want to handle all events it
不想处理所有事件
there are some events that don't need to
有些事件不需要
be to persist anything as a result and
结果是坚持一切
so it actually returns a type of
所以它实际上返回一种
optional if the event is not one that
如果事件不是一个可选事件
it's interesting it will return an empty
有趣的是它将返回一个空
optional so the next thing we want to do
可选，所以我们接下来要做的是
is filter out all those empty so we use
过滤掉所有那些空的，所以我们使用
filter to do that and we'll use
过滤器做到这一点，我们将使用
optionally as present so if if that
视情况而定，如果存在
method returned a document then it'll
方法返回了文档，然后它将
still be in the stream otherwise that
仍然在流中，否则
after this filter operation there won't
在执行此过滤器操作之后，
be any element in that stream for that
成为那个流中的任何元素
now next thing so our message is still
现在下一件事，所以我们的信息仍然
wrapped inside an optional let's unwrap
包裹在一个可选的让我们解开
it using optional yet so now we have our
它使用可选的，所以现在我们有了
our documents that are preferring to our
我们偏爱我们的文件
stream not as optionals just as direct
流不像可选一样直接
elements and so now we can actually
元素，所以现在我们可以
handle them we will use flatmap
处理它们，我们将使用平面图
completion stage so we have a reactive
完成阶段，所以我们有一个反应
or an asynchronous elasticsearch store
或异步Elasticsearch存储
here Sordo index store that store and
在这里，Sordo索引存储
we'll pass in the document
我们将传递文件
it has in the message their message dr.
在消息中有他们的消息博士。
payload now the result of that store
有效负载现在是该存储的结果
operation is a completion stage of done
操作是完成的完成阶段
which is just a unit operation we're
这只是一个单元操作
going to map that to convert it back to
打算将其转换回
the message because after storing it we
该消息，因为存储后，我们
want to then acknowledge the message
想再确认消息
from the Kafka queue so we now have
从卡夫卡队列开始，所以我们现在有了
we've stored it but we've still got our
我们已经存储了它，但仍然有我们的
string with messages so we can do no
带有消息的字符串，所以我们不能
completion stage and we can invoke the
完成阶段，我们可以调用
the Act which once again is amazing
该法案再次令人惊讶
which is why we use mass flatmap
这就是为什么我们使用大众平面图
completion stage and after that we've
完成阶段之后，我们已经
actually done everything that we need to
实际上完成了我们需要做的一切
do so we just terminate the stream with
这样做，我们只需终止流
this null up on on it on each major
在每个专业上都没有涉及
element and then we can return that as a
元素，然后我们可以将其返回为
subscriber of message events so having
消息事件的订阅者，因此具有
implemented that I've got this
实现我已经有了这个
application then in the background logon
然后在后台登录
automatically detects changes to corrode
自动检测腐蚀变化
recompiles and restarts services i
重新编译并重新启动服务
should mention that this application is
应该提到这个应用程序是
written in in logon which is a reactive
用登录方式写的，这是一种反应
local services framework so that should
本地服务框架，因此应该
have reloaded and we do the search again
已重新加载，我们再次进行搜索
we don't see the current price and the
我们看不到当前价格和
reason is because there's something else
原因是因为还有别的东西
that we haven't implemented yet but
我们还没有实施，但是
before I get to showing that I'll move
在我展示我会动之前
on to the next slide so another thing
转到下一张幻灯片，另一件事
that's come up in discussions of race in
这是关于种族竞赛的讨论
in micro profile is the possibility of a
在微观轮廓上是
CQRS spec now say QR S stands for
CQRS规范现在说QR S代表
command query responsibility segregation
命令查询责任分离
and it's about separating the
这是关于分离
responsibility of handling commands from
负责处理来自
the responsibility of handing hailing
冰雹的责任
clear
明确
is such that they can be handled in
这样它们就可以在
different databases they can be scaled
可以扩展的不同数据库
in apparently and more importantly what
显然，更重要的是
we're interested in here is we don't
我们对这里感兴趣，我们不
want them to be able to impact each
希望他们能够影响每个
other so if a query fails - if the query
其他，如果查询失败-如果查询
handling fails for some reason that
处理由于某种原因而失败
shouldn't stop our commands from being
不应该停止我们的命令
processed and you would have earlier in
已处理，您将早于
the presentation I talked about how
我谈到的演示文稿
about how we can handle about how if you
关于如何处理您的问题
publish directly to a message broker
直接发布到消息代理
after you do an operation such as an
在执行诸如
update on the database then you have a
更新数据库，然后您有一个
level of coupling with your message
与您的消息的耦合程度
broker heater CQRS can be used to to
经纪人加热器CQRS可用于
decouple that your your persisting of
解耦您的坚持
your handling of your command from then
从那时起您对命令的处理
publishing those events to the message
将这些事件发布到消息中
broker so they can update queries so
经纪人，以便他们可以更新查询，以便
let's take a look back in our service
让我们回顾一下我们的服务
and we're going to move now into a
现在我们要进入
different service into the bidding
不同的服务进入招标
service and this is the code that I've
服务，这是我所拥有的代码
implemented that publishers they're in
实施他们所在的发布商
love now I'm not going to show the
现在爱我不会显示
actual persistence for the bidding
投标的实际持续时间
service but what the bidding service
服务，但是竞标服务是什么
does is when it it's using event
确实是在使用事件时
sourcing and so rather than storing the
采购，而不是存储
current state of an option such as you
诸如您这样的选项的当前状态
know it's this is the current price and
知道这是当前价格，
this is the current winning bidder and
这是目前的中标者，
the current fee option is still running
当前的费用选项仍在运行
rather than store in that state it
而不是存储在那种状态
simply stores all the events that
只需存储所有事件
happened and computes the state from the
发生并从中计算状态
event so oxygens started this bid was
事件，因此氧气开始竞标是
placed this bid was placed the option is
已放置此出价已放置选项
finished
完了
and because when it does that it stores
并且因为它在存储时会存储
those events in an event log that event
这些事件记录在该事件中
log can be consumed asynchronously it by
日志可以被异步使用
another process in this case this
在这种情况下的另一个过程
publish event log method and so we have
发布事件日志方法，所以我们有
this decoupling from the persistence
这种与持久性的脱钩
where these where where these events was
这些事件在哪里
were persisted and and the thing that
被坚持，而那件事
then goes and in another process
然后在另一个过程中
potentially
潜在地
another machine at a different time goes
在不同时间的另一台机器
and reads that event load and publishers
并读取该事件的负载和发布者
adapter Kafka so you can see once again
卡夫卡适配器，让您可以再次看到
this this time it's not a subscriber
这次不是订户
it's a processor which means that
这是一个处理器，这意味着
transforms messages we we create a
转换我们创建的消息
builder and we filter them to only
生成器，我们将它们过滤为
publish the ones that we want to filter
发布我们要过滤的内容
and then we do some transformations on
然后我们对
them and we end up converting these
他们，我们最终转换这些
incoming messages of the auction event
拍卖活动的传入消息
that's what gets persisted to the
那就是坚持不懈的
database to these bid event which is
这些出价事件的数据库
what we are not publishing to cover and
我们没有发布的内容
what we're missing here is annotations
我们在这里缺少的是注释
to be able to declare this so this these
能够宣布这一点，所以这些
are the reactive messaging annotations
是反应式消息传递注释
and here I'm saying the provider is the
在这里我说的是提供商
event log so this is so this isn't
事件日志，所以这不是
actually getting messages from the
实际上从
message broker here it's getting
消息代理在这里越来越
messages for our database from our CQRS
来自CQRS的数据库消息
event stream and they're going to be
事件流，他们将成为
users incoming messages and then
用户收到的消息，然后
outgoing we will publish to the bid
即将发布的出价
event queue in Kafka and so now I've
卡夫卡的事件队列，所以现在我已经
made these changes and when when logon
进行了这些更改以及何时登录
picks that up recompiles where he starts
在他开始的地方捡起来重新编译
my service I can go I can hit Search and
我可以去的服务我可以点击搜索，
hopefully it should just show the
希望它应该显示
current price I'm not sure why it's not
目前的价格，我不确定为什么不
doing that
那样做
we'll try posting another bid just for
我们将尝试仅针对
good measure
好的措施
and so the price now there is is
所以现在的价格是
published
已发表
now unfortunately I've been in this demo
现在很不幸，我去过这个演示
a number of times before and what
很多次之前和什么
happens there is is the current price
碰巧有当前价格
just comes up and I'll have to go back
刚来，我必须回去
and work out exactly why I didn't come
并弄清楚为什么我不来
up then it possibly there was a
然后可能有一个
something wasn't connected to Kafka
卡夫卡没有任何联系
sometimes in development of fine Kafka
有时在发展优质的卡夫卡
than be a bit finicky but I'm an
比有点挑剔，但我是
important thing to to that if the demo
重要的是如果演示
works or what have demonstrated is that
作品或证明的是
we actually had a self-healing system
我们实际上有一个自我修复系统
there when when I am at some stage as
当我在某个阶段时
you saw I hadn't even implemented the
你看到我什至没有实施
publish now we had published directly to
现在发布，我们直接发布到
cough go after do an hour operation then
咳嗽后做一个小时的手术然后
we would have had our system wouldn't
我们本来不会有我们的系统
have ever got that those current price
曾经得到那些当前的价格
those bit events because if because they
这些位事件，因为如果因为
were lost in history
迷失了历史
you can't republish you can't redo
你不能重新发布你不能重做
something from the past but when you
过去的事，但是当你
work with streams when you take a stream
串流时使用串流
oriented approach to the system then
面向系统的方法
you can resume you can resume that
你可以恢复你可以恢复
processing at any time and so you get
随时处理，所以您得到
this
这个
these self-healing property
这些自我修复的属性
probabilities where the stream itself is
流本身所在的概率
what continues pushing your your system
什么继续推动您的系统
to be to be consistent
保持一致
and so that's the end of the
这样就结束了
presentation there are some links here
演示这里有一些链接
that I've got you can see the micro
我有你可以看到微
profile reactant streams operators spec
轮廓反应物流操作员规范
is the documentation for the operators
是运营商的文件
which I showed before and the Mike
我之前和麦克展示过
profile reactive messaging spec so I
配置响应式消息传递规范，因此我
might check if there are questions now I
可能会检查我现在是否有问题
can't actually see any any questions in
实际上看不到任何问题
the chat
聊天室
oh you don't yeah you want to write them
哦，你不，你想写他们
out to me so um let me see trying to
让我出去，让我看看试图
figure out if I can point to you the
弄清楚我能否指向你
questions but nevertheless so one of the
问题，但尽管如此，其中之一
questions that we have is what is CQRS
我们遇到的问题是什么是CQRS
and then you know the link was provided
然后您知道提供了链接
for for that but if you wanted to go
为此，但如果你想去
over that did you have any comments so
在那边你有什么意见吗
yeah I did mention CQRS early in the
是的，我确实在早期提到了CQRS
presentation without explaining and then
演示而无需解释，然后
I did explain a bit more detail later
我确实在稍后解释了更多细节
but just to go over it again it's
但是只是要再遍一遍
command query responsibility segregation
命令查询责任分离
and the idea is to separate your
想法是将您的
commands which are your write operations
您的写操作命令
from your queries which are your read
从您的查询中读取
operations and so you what you end up
操作，所以你最终会得到什么
with is you do some comma you handle
与你做一些逗号处理
your write operations and then you have
你的写操作，然后你有
a stream of events that are the output
作为输出的事件流
of your write operations whether it's
您的写操作是否
event sourcing where the events
事件来源
themselves are what you persist or in
自己就是你坚持或坚持的东西
addition to doing some updates on the
除了对
crud database you might persist some
Crud数据库，您可能会坚持一些
events to an event table you can then
事件到事件表中，然后
consume those events usually they will
通常会消耗这些事件
have some sort of offset and so you can
有某种偏移，所以你可以
track where you are in two bit offset
跟踪您在两位偏移中的位置
which means when you fail or when
这意味着您何时失败或何时
something goes wrong you can resume from
出现问题，您可以从中恢复
that offset and it allows you to to be
该偏移量，它使您能够
able to do that processing on different
能够在不同的位置进行处理
on different machines you can use
您可以在不同的机器上使用
different database technical
不同的数据库技术
so example here I'm using events or I'm
所以这里的例子我正在使用事件或
using elastic search for the search
使用弹性搜索进行搜索
service which is a different technology
服务是一种不同的技术
to Cassandra which is what's been used
给卡桑德拉使用的是
in the item service and bid service and
在项目服务和出价服务中，以及
and because it's streams based you can
而且由于它是基于流的，因此您可以
take advantage of the fact that but you
利用事实，但你
can let the infrastructure manage your
可以让基础架构管理您的
streams for you to manage your favorite
为您管理自己喜欢的视频流
but the failure rate rise distribution
但故障率上升分布
right another question is is do you
对另一个问题是你
support or is this working with vertex
支持还是与顶点一起使用
yes so I'm vertex one of the
是的，所以我是其中之一
implementations of reactive streams
反应流的实现
operators is it has been implemented by
运营商是否已实施
Red Hat on Eric's Java with we'd also
我们还将与Eric的Java一起使用Red Hat
support in in vertex and indeed the the
在顶点上的支持，的确
Red Hat's messaging implementation is
红帽的消息传递实现是
built on vertex so the work the work
建立在顶点上，这样工作就可以了
that I'm doing is with arca archa
我正在做的是与阿卡·阿卡
streams and and log on but if you go to
流并登录，但如果您转到
Red Hat's microphone implementation
红帽的麦克风实现
you'll get support on on vertex
您将在顶点上获得支持
another question is what is the benefit
另一个问题是有什么好处
of using this over the plane Kafka
在飞机上使用这个卡夫卡
streams API yeah so Kafka streams is
流API是的，所以Kafka流是
Kafka - Kafka you can do Kafka connect
卡夫卡-卡夫卡你可以做卡夫卡连接
but it's very limited
但是非常有限
Kafka streams they say they support
他们说他们支持的卡夫卡流
event sourcing but they only support
事件采购，但他们仅支持
something that looks vaguely like event
看起来像事件的东西
sourcing it doesn't support commands
采购不支持命令
it's just events that must be handled
这只是必须处理的事件
and can't be rejected which is a
并且不能被拒绝，这是一个
fundamental thing of then sourcing is
那么采购的根本是
that you can validate and reject
您可以验证和拒绝
commands so if if you need to do cuff go
命令，如果您需要做袖带
to Kafka processing then then Kafka
到卡夫卡加工然后是卡夫卡
streams is great but what this gives you
流很棒，但是这给了你什么
is is is so much more you can as you saw
你所能看到的是更多
you can connect and an event log in a
您可以连接，并在
database to your to your to to to cough
数据库到你到你去咳嗽
like you it's also there's no Kafka
像你一样，那里也没有卡夫卡
specific code there all that in or there
那里或那里所有的特定代码
doesn't have to be any Kafka specific
不一定是任何Kafka特有的
code in your application so you can you
您的应用程序中的代码，以便您可以
can have you can do your vet Kafka to
可以让你做你的兽医卡夫卡
calculate vent processing without being
计算通风口处理而无需
tired to cover and be able to move to
累了掩盖，并能够移动到
different message brokers for example
例如，不同的消息代理
the cloud technologies like kinases or
激酶或其他云技术
Azure event hubs a very tough girl like
Azure活动中心是一个非常坚强的女孩，例如
you can your your code will be portable
你可以你的代码将是可移植的
to those so so this allows you to to do
对那些，所以这使你可以做
things without the vendor locking that
没有供应商锁定的东西
you get with Kafka streams okay let me
你与卡夫卡流在一起，好吧，让我
see I need to thank micro profile
看到我要感谢微简介
eclipse micro profile community for kind
蚀微轮廓社区
of answering questions and and and also
回答问题以及
they're they're quite active in the chat
他们是他们在聊天中非常活跃
as well so let me see I think you
也让我看看我想你
already said that
已经说过
the example you provided is on the
您提供的示例位于
github is that right yet the the example
github是正确的例子
happens itself I think I have a version
发生本身，我想我有一个版本
of it which is a bit different from
其中有点不同于
another presentation but I can publish
另一个演示文稿，但我可以发表
it to two to github yeah
它到两个到github是的
I'll publish it to this is where I'll
我将其发布到这里
publish up to but that doesn't exist yet
最多发布，但尚不存在
but Jakarta - Hey - reactive just
但是雅加达-嘿-只是反应而已
streaming that's where you'll be able to
流媒体，您将能够在其中
find it probably five minutes after this
在此之后五分钟找到它
presentation is finished that's
演示文稿完成了
fantastic
太棒了
maybe if you don't mind put it on the on
也许如果您不介意把它放在上面
your last slide so people can view it
您的最后一张幻灯片，以便人们查看
from that perspective as well and have
从这个角度来看
the link there okay any more questions
链接那里还有其他问题
comments for James
詹姆斯的评论
we want to keep James around to answer
我们想让詹姆斯在身边回答
more questions so please if there are
还有更多问题，如果有，请
any questions or comments whatsoever on
关于任何问题或评论
the talks please put it in the chat
谈话请放在聊天中
we're super excited to see you that you
我们很高兴见到你
down then and then that there is
然后再下来
activity on the chat okay so if there
聊天活动好吧，如果有
isn't anything else a reminder that in a
没什么其他提醒
month we will have another call I'm just
一个月，我们将再打一个电话
about to set it up I'm hoping to either
即将设置我希望
have a Malaysian or Sebastian - nur to
有马来西亚人或塞巴斯蒂安人-要
have their talk talks so stay tuned and
有他们的谈话话题，请继续关注
kind of monitor for the date and time
日期和时间的监视器
and in the meanwhile I want to thank
同时我要感谢
James very very much it is greatly
詹姆斯非常非常非常
appreciated and yeah we'll stay in touch
感谢，是的，我们会保持联系
and we know where to find James if we
如果我们知道我们在哪里可以找到詹姆斯
need him to you know provide more
需要他知道你提供更多
information with regards to streaming or
有关流的信息或
reactive streaming or anything else bye
反应式流式传输或其他任何方式
for now and staying warm particularly
暂时保持温暖
asked on the northern hemisphere where
问北半球在哪里
it's so freezing okay thank you everyone
太冻结了，谢谢大家
and we'll be in touch thank you
我们会保持联系，谢谢
you
您